<speak xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" version="1.0">
  <p>
    <s>Large Language Models have changed the game forever.</s>
    <s>It's never been easier to generate code, but it's also never been harder to know if
      your code is as robust as ChatGPT would lead you to believe.</s>
    <s>Sure, you can scaffold out a React app from scratch with one prompt... but can you
      vibe your way around a real-world codebase?</s>
    <s>What do you do when your app no longer fits in the context window?</s>
    <s>What do you do when you are out of API credits?</s>
    <s>And are you sure that the LLM is not hallucinating?</s>
  </p>

  <break time="800ms"></break>

  <p>
    <s>Introducing Testeranto, the AI-powered BDD test framework for TypeScript projects.</s>
    <s>It's a fresh new way of testing TypeScript code, one that harnesses the raw power of
      LLM-generated code with the control of Behavior Driven Design.</s>
  </p>

  <break time="800ms"></break>

  <p>
    <s>Here's how it works:</s>
    <s>You wrap your code in a 'semantic layer' that exposes it to the Gherkin-like
      directives Given, When, and Then.</s>
    <s>Then, you add some behavior specs, written in a strongly typed DSL that even a
      stakeholder can understand.</s>
    <s>Testeranto will bundle and execute your tests on its custom multi-platform
      environment.</s>
    <s>That means it can run tests in the browser, as well as on the server-side.</s>
    <s>The results of those tests, along with your source code, your documentation and your
      feature specifications are all gathered into a precisely tuned prompt.</s>
    <s>With the press of a button, Testeranto will launch that prompt, and auto-magically
      fix the broken tests.</s>
  </p>

  <break time="1s"></break>

  <p>
    <s>Testeranto is more than a test platform.</s>
    <s>It's living documentation and a test reporter too.</s>
    <s>All the data that is fed into the LLM context is also used to build a static website,
      which is easily deployed to GitHub Pages.</s>
    <s>This puts the BDD specs, the test results and the test artifacts in one convenient
      package.</s>
    <s>Allowing you to know the health of your codebase at a glance.</s>
  </p>

  <break time="1s"></break>

  <p>
    <s>Do you think that your project could benefit from Testeranto?</s>
    <s>Then contact <say-as interpret-as="email">testeranto-dev@gmail.com</say-as> to get
      put to the front of the list for our beta program.</s>
    <s>And get free support for life.</s>
  </p>
</speak>
